l don't know what I'm gonna do.
(Bernadette:)I'm supposed to marry Howard
in a couple weeks...
(Bernadette:)...and I'm not sure I even know
who the man is anymore.
(Amy:)I'm curious what's bothering you most...
(Amy:)...the borderline incest, the prostitute...
(Amy:)...or group sex with the girl
dressed as the children's cartoon.
(Penny:)Remember when we went over things that
would be helpful and things that wouldn't?
(Sheldon:)Right.
- And that was?...
- Not.
(Bernadette:)When I first met Howard,
he seemed so innocent to me.
(Bernadette:)Just a sweet little guy
who lives with his mother.
(Penny:)If that's what you like, I'll take you to the
comic book store. The place is full of them.
(Bernadette:)Wait a minute.
(Bernadette:)You set me up with Howard.
(Bernadette:)Did you know about
all the creepy stuff he was into?
Oh, a little. You hear stuff.
Why didn't you tell me?
l was gonna but I didn't think it
would go past the first date.
When it did, I thought it wouldn't go past
you meeting his mother.